The Tyrells are a problem.
The Tyrells helped us
defeat Stannis Baratheon.
You must see Highgarden.
I don't think the queen
would let me leave King's Landing.
Once I marry Joffrey,
I'll be queen.
And if you were
to marry Loras...
You must give yourself
to the Lord of Light.
- I have a wife.
- She's shut away in a tower.
And she's given you no sons,
only stillborns.
I lost one son to the Kingslayer,
strangled with a chain.
I grieve for
your sons, my lord.
I don't want your grief.
I want my vengeance.
Do that again
and I'll take your other hand.
- What value was the mill?
- I seized an opportunity.
We took hostages--
Willem Lannister, Martyn Lannister.
Willem and Martyn Lannister
are 14 years old.
I'm not your enemy.
This woman is evil!
Take him to the dungeon
and lock him in a cell.
You want to
assassinate a girl?
- Based on whose information?
- Ser Jorah Mormont.
He is serving as advisor
to the Targaryens.
You bring us the whispers
of a traitor.
Beric Dondarrion?
If you mean to murder me,
then bloody well
get on with it.
You'll die soon enough,
but it won't be murder.
I sentence you
to trial by combat.
Is it done, then?
Dracarys.
♪ Game of Thrones 3x05 ♪
Kissed by Fire
Original Air Date on April 28, 2013
♪
Lord, cast your light
upon us.
Lord of Light, defend us.
Show us the truth.
Strike this man down
if he is guilty.
Give strength to his sword
if he is true.
Lord of Light,
give us wisdom.
For the night is dark
and full of terrors.
Get back.
Guilty. Guilty. Guilty.
Guilty. Guilty.
Guilty.
Kill him!
Lord, cast your light
upon this man, your servant.
Bring him back
from death and darkness.
His flame has been
extinguished.
Restore it.
For the night is dark
and full of terrors.
- Lord, cast...
- Arya, don't!
Bring him back
from death and darkness...
No!
Let go of me!
Let me go!
Looks like their god likes me
more than your butcher's boy.
Burn in hell!
He will.
But not today.
Orell says there are crows
patrolling on the Wall.
Tell me what you know.
There are four
to a patrol--
two builders to check
for structural damage,
two rangers to watch
for enemies.
How often do these
patrols go out?
It varies.
If I knew where on the Wall we
were heading, I could tell you.
You'd like to know that.
There are 19 castles
guarding the Wall.
How many are manned?
Three.
You sure of that?
Which three?
Castle Black.
Aye, Castle Black.
Everyone knows
Castle Black.
Which others?
Eastwatch-by-the-Sea
and the Shadow Tower.
How many men remain
in Castle Black?
- 1,000.
- Liar.
What happens to your eagle
after I kill you?
Does he drift away like a
kite with his strings cut
or does he just flop
dead to the ground?
He's no crow.
Just 'cause you want him inside
you don't make him one of us.
I'm not afraid of you.
I like you, boy.
But if you lie to me,
I'll pull your guts out
through your throat.
1,000 men.
We'll find out soon enough.
I don't need you
to protect me.
Of course you do.
Who stopped Rattleshirt
when he was about to cut your throat?
Who vouched for you
with Mance?
It seems
you owe me a debt.
- Give it back.
- Well, I stole it.
It's mine.
If you want it, come steal it back.
Ygritte!
Seven hells.
Is Orell right?
Are you still a crow?
It's time you
proved yourself.
Ygritte.
You swore some vows.
I want you to break 'em.
I want you to see me.
All of me.
We shouldn't.
We should.
Why are you
still dressed?
You know nothing,
Jon Sno--
That thing you did
with your mouth--
is that what lords
do to their ladies in the South?
I don't know.
I just wanted to kiss
you there is all.
Hmm.
You seemed to like it.
Aye, I liked it some.
Who taught you that?
There's been no one else.
Only you.
A maid.
You were a maid.
I was a man
of the Night's Watch.
How about you?
Were you a maid?
What do you think?
- Who was he?
- Just a boy.
He came trading
with his brothers.
He had red hair like me.
Kissed by fire.
But...
he was weak.
Not like you.
That was the first one.
Then there was
this Thenn boy.
Spoke no Common, but gods,
he was built like a mammoth.
Yeah, thanks.
I think I've heard enough.
We'd best get back.
Tormund--
I'm not done
with you yet.
How long's it been
since you had a bath?
Let's not go back.
Let's stay here
a while longer.
I don't ever want
to leave this cave, Jon Snow.
Not ever.
I want my gold.
It says it clearly
right there on that note
you'll be repaid in full
when the war is over.
Piss on that!
You're nothing but thieves.
We're outlaws.
Outlaws steal.
You're lucky
we didn't kill you.
Come try it, archer.
I'll shove those arrows
up your ass.
You can't let him go.
He's a murderer. He's guilty.
- Not in the eyes of god.
- You can't!
Enough! The judgment
isn't ours to make.
Go in peace,
Sandor Clegane.
The Lord of Light
isn't done with you yet.
Riders coming through!
The Kingslayer.
Down!
On your knees.
Lord Bolton, I give you
the Kingslayer.
Pick him up, Locke.
You've lost a hand.
No, my lord,
he has it here.
- Take this away.
- Send it to his father?
You'll hold your tongue
unless you want to lose it.
Cut her free.
Apologies, my lady.
You're under
my protection now.
Thank you, my lord.
Find suitable rooms
for our guests.
We'll speak later.
Lord Bolton.
Is there word
from the capital?
You haven't heard?
Stannis Baratheon laid siege
to King's Landing.
Sailed into Blackwater Bay.
Stormed the gates
with thousands of men.
And your sister...
How can I put this?
Your sister...
is alive and well.
Your father's forces
prevailed.
Ser Jaime isn't well.
Take him to Qyburn.
- Will I die?
- No.
The corruption
has spread.
I fear it must
be cut away.
The safest course would be
to take the whole arm off.
Then you'll die.
You're no maester.
Where's your chain?
The Citadel
stripped me of it.
They found some
of my experiments
too bold.
I can leave your upper arm,
make the cut at your elbow.
I don't need my right hand
to kill you.
I can take away
the rotting flesh
and try and burn out
the corruption
- with boiling wine.
- Mmm.
With any luck,
that will suffice.
You'll need
milk of the poppy.
- No milk of the poppy.
- There will be pain.
- I'll scream.
- Quite a bit of pain.
I'll scream loudly.
Lord Baelish.
Your Grace.
I wonder if I might
ask you for a favor.
Of course, Your Grace.
I have reason to believe
that House Tyrell
do not hold the crown's
best interests at heart.
I see. And have you shared these
suspicions with Lord Tywin?
My father's a practical man.
He appreciates facts.
Myself, I often
find them a hindrance.
And he appreciates those
who aid his family, as you well know.
He's almost as generous
to those who help us
as he is unpleasant
towards those who don't.
You have a good working
relationship with the Tyrells.
I thought you might look into it
before you leave the capital.
- I shall do my best.
- Thank you.
And your best will prove better than
when I asked you to locate Arya Stark?
I assure you
that it will.
Gods, boy, that's enough.
We're not in a tavern.
- Pardon, my lady.
- No need to speak.
Are there any figs?
Fetch some.
I always take figs
midafternoon.
They help move the bowels.
To what do I owe
this summons?
Thank you for seeing me,
my lady.
I had hoped we might discuss
a few financial matters.
I climbed all those steps to discuss
financial matters?
It's the royal wedding.
I'm told you had a hand
in planning it.
Naturally.
It's shaping up to be
a very involved affair.
The word extravagant
has been used.
What good
is the word extravagant
if it can't be used
to describe a royal wedding?
- I understand that.
- Good.
But, as Master of Coin,
it falls upon me
to calculate the cost
for the crown.
As of now,
it's a huge expense.
And?
And we're at war,
Lady Olenna.
Oh, I'd nearly
forgotten.
Yes, and maintaining
supply lines--
I can't think
how it slipped my mind.
What is it,
12,000 infantrymen
the Tyrell family
has supplied?
1,800 mounted lances.
2,000 in support.
Provisions so this city
might survive the winter.
A million bushels
of wheat.
Half a million bushels each
of barley, oats, and rye.
20,000 head of cattle.
50,000 sheep.
You don't have to lecture me
about wartime expenses.
I'm quite familiar
with them.
And we are so grateful
for your contributions
which are necessary
for the preservation of the realm.
As is a royal wedding.
The people are hungry
for more than just food.
They crave distractions.
And if we don't provide them,
they'll create their own.
And their distractions
are likely to end
with us being torn
to pieces.
A royal wedding
is much safer.
- Wouldn't you say?
- I would.
And traditionally
paid for
by the royal family.
I was told you were
drunk, impertinent,
and thoroughly debauched.
You can imagine
my disappointment
at finding nothing
but a browbeaten bookkeeper.
Where did you go
for them, Volantis?
- My lady--
- Oh, very well.
I won't have it said
that House Tyrell
refuses to play
its part.
We'll pay for half
the expenses
and the celebrations
will go on as planned.
- Is that sufficient?
- Quite sufficient. Thank you.
Very good, then.
That's settled. Good day.
Give me that.
What are you doing?
Just mending
Lord Beric's armor.
Why?
I'm going to stay on
and smith for the Brotherhood.
Have you lost your mind?
When the Lannisters find this place,
you think they'll spare the smiths?
They'll cave your head in
with your own helmet.
The Lannisters wanted to kill me long
before I joined the Brotherhood.
You don't have to do this.
I want to.
They need good men.
Robb needs good men, too.
We're leaving tomorrow.
- And then you--
- What? Serve him?
I've served men
my entire life.
I served Master Mott
at King's Landing
and he sold me
to the Watch.
I served Lord Tywin
at Harrenhal,
wondering every day
if I'd get tortured or killed.
I'm done serving.
You just said you were
serving Lord Beric.
He may be their leader,
but they chose him.
These men are brothers.
They're a family.
I've never had a family.
I can be your family.
You wouldn't be
my family.
You'd be "my lady."
Willem.
Willem!
- Is this a rescue?
- Lannister filth! Take him!
Please, I didn't do anything.
I'm just a squire.
Please--
Bring them in.
Is that all of them?
It took five of you to murder
two unarmed squires?
Not murder,
Your Grace.
Vengeance.
Vengeance?
Those boys didn't
kill your sons.
I saw Harrion die
on the battlefield and Torrhen--
Was strangled
by the Kingslayer.
- They were his kin.
- They were boys!
Look at them.
Tell your mother
to look at them.
She killed them
as much as I.
My mother had nothing
to do with this.
This was your treason.
It's treason
to free your enemies.
In war, you kill
your enemies.
Did your father
not teach you that, boy?
Leave him.
Aye.
Leave me to the king.
He wants to give me
a scolding before he sets me free.
That's how he deals
with treason.
Our King in the North.
Or should I call him
the King Who Lost
the North?
Escort Lord Karstark
to the dungeon.
Hang the rest.
Mercy, sire!
I didn't kill anyone.
I only watched
for the guards.
This one was only
the watcher.
Hang him last so he can watch
the others die.
Please! Please, no.
They made me do it!
They made me!
Word of this
can't leave Riverrun.
They were Tywin
Lannister's nephews.
The Lannisters
pay their debts.
They never stop
talking about it.
Would you make me a liar
as well as a murderer?
It wouldn't be lying.
We will bury them
and remain silent
until the war is done.
I'm not fighting
for justice
if I don't serve justice
to murderers in my ranks,
no matter how highborn.
He has to die.
The Karstarks
are Northmen.
They won't forgive
the killing of their lord.
Your mother's right.
If you do this, the Karstarks will
abandon you.
You tended to their wounds.
You brought them supper.
Now they're dead.
And more boys will keep dying
until this war is over.
You need Karstark men
to end it.
Spare his life.
Keep him as a hostage.
A hostage.
Tell the Karstarks
that as long as they remain loyal,
he will not be harmed.
The blood of the First Men
flows through my veins
as much as yours, boy.
I fought the Mad King
for your father.
I fought Joffrey
for you.
We are kin--
Stark and Karstark.
That didn't stop you
from betraying me.
And it won't save you now.
I don't want it
to save me.
I want it to haunt you
to the end of your days.
Kneel, my lord.
Rickard Karstark,
Lord of Karhold,
here in sight of gods and men,
I sentence you to die.
Would you speak
a final word?
Kill me
and be cursed.
You are no king of mine.
Joffrey.
Cersei.
Ilyn Payne.
Ser Meryn.
The Hound.
What are you
going to do with me?
At first light
we'll ride for Riverrun.
Your brother's there now.
He'll make a contribution
to our cause
and you can go home.
I'm a hostage
and you're selling me.
Don't think of it
that way.
- But it is that way.
- It is.
- And it isn't.
- More is than isn't.
Beric admired your father
a great deal, you know.
He wanted to refuse
your ransom altogether.
- So why don't you?
- We need the gold.
Do I frighten you, child?
No.
You're angry with me.
And I don't blame you.
But letting him go
was the right thing.
I have more reason than most
to want him hanged.
- I thought he killed you.
- He did.
But how...?
Thoros...
how many times
have you brought me back?
It's the Lord of Light
brings you back.
I'm just the lucky drunk
who says the words.
- How many times?
- Five, I think.
No, this makes six.
Six.
There was the first time--
the Mountain.
Show her.
Lance right through
the chest.
Then I was stabbed
in the belly.
Then it was an arrow
in the back.
And that axe in the side.
Then the Lannisters caught me
and executed me for treason.
Was it a hanging
or a dagger in the eye?
Both.
Fuckers couldn't decide.
And the Hound makes six.
Second time I've been
killed by a Clegane.
You'd think you'd learn.
It's not getting
any easier, you know.
I know.
Every time I come back,
I'm a bit less.
Pieces of you
get chipped away.
Could you bring back
a man without a head?
Not six times.
Just once.
I don't think it works
that way, child.
He was a good man,
Ned Stark.
He's at rest now,
somewhere.
I would never wish
my life upon him.
I would.
You're alive.
Lord, cast your light
upon me.
Protect me
in the darkness.
Burn away my sins.
Help me serve you.
Use me as you will.
For the night is dark
and full of terrors.
I have prayed day and night
for you to come to me.
My lady.
I meant to come sooner.
- The battle--
- I know of your troubles, my king.
The Lady Melisandre
has told me everything.
Yes, of course.
You mustn't despair.
Your claim is true.
- You will be victorious.
- I believed that once.
You are
the one god's champion
and the finest man
I've ever known.
Selyse.
I've broken a sacred vow.
I've sinned.
- No.
- I've wronged you.
- I have shamed you.
- You're doing god's work.
You don't understand.
The Red Woman--
the Lady Melisandre--
I know, Stannis.
The Lady Melisandre
has told me everything.
No act done in service
of the Lord of Light
can ever be a sin.
When she told me,
I wept with joy.
Oh, my sweet boys.
Petyr, Tommard,
Edric.
I thank god
every day
for bringing
Melisandre to us.
She gave you a son.
I gave you...
- nothing.
- That's not true.
So you've come
to see her as well?
There is no need.
You must keep away
from such distractions.
She's my daughter.
I want to see her.
You are a king.
You don't need
my permission.
♪ Under the sea ♪
♪ I know, I know ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ The birds have scales ♪
♪ And the fish take wing ♪
♪ I know, I know ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh... ♪
Shireen.
Father!
You've grown
since I last saw you.
Mother said you fought
in a battle.
Did you win?
No.
Did the Onion Knight
come back with you?
He did.
He fought bravely.
He hasn't come
to visit me.
He said he'd bring me back a
present from the capital.
He won't be visiting, child.
Why not?
He's my friend.
Look.
He made this for me.
But don't tell Mother
I have it.
It's a secret.
Mother doesn't like
the Onion Knight.
Ser Davos
is a traitor.
He's rotting in a dungeon
cell for his crime.
Best forget him.
Not so hard.
You'll scrub the skin off.
What are you
doing here?
I need a bath.
Help me out
of these rags.
Now get out.
There's another tub.
This one suits me fine.
Don't worry.
I'm not interested.
If I faint, pull me out.
I don't intend to be the first Lannister
to die in a bathtub.
Why should I care
how you die?
You swore a solemn vow,
remember?
You're supposed to get me to
King's Landing in one piece.
Not going so well, is it?
No wonder Renly died
with you guarding him.
That was unworthy.
Forgive me.
You protected me
better than most--
- Don't you mock me.
- I'm apologizing.
I'm sick of fighting.
Let's call a truce.
You need trust
to have a truce.
I trust you.
There it is.
There's the look.
I've seen it for 17 years
on face after face.
You all despise me.
Kingslayer.
Oathbreaker.
A man without honor.
You've heard of wildfire?
Of course.
The Mad King
was obsessed with it.
He loved to watch
people burn,
the way their skin
blackened and blistered
and melted
off their bones.
He burned lords
he didn't like.
He burned Hands
who disobeyed him.
He burned anyone
who was against him.
Before long, half the country
was against him.
Aerys saw traitors
everywhere.
So he had his pyromancer
place caches of wildfire
all over the city--
beneath the Sept
of Baelor
and the slums
of Flea Bottom.
Under houses,
stables, taverns.
Even beneath
the Red Keep itself.
Finally,
the day
of reckoning came.
Robert Baratheon
marched on the capital
after his victory
at the Trident.
But my father
arrived first
with the whole Lannister
army at his back,
promising to defend the city
against the rebels.
I knew my father
better than that.
He's never been one
to pick the losing side.
I told the Mad King
as much.
I urged him
to surrender peacefully.
But the king didn't
listen to me.
He didn't listen to Varys
who tried to warn him.
But he did listen
to Grand Maester Pycelle,
that grey, sunken cunt.
"You can trust
the Lannisters," he said.
"The Lannisters
have always been
true friends
of the crown."
So we opened the gates
and my father
sacked the city.
Once again,
I came to the king,
begging him to surrender.
He told me to...
bring him
my father's head.
Then he...
turned to his pyromancer.
"Burn them all,"
he said.
"Burn them
in their homes.
Burn them
in their beds."
Tell me,
if your precious Renly
commanded you to kill
your own father
and stand by while
thousands of men,
women, and children
burned alive,
would you have done it?
Would you have
kept your oath then?
First, I killed
the pyromancer.
And then when the king
turned to flee,
I drove my sword
into his back.
"Burn them all,"
he kept saying.
"Burn them all."
I don't think
he expected to die.
He-- he meant to...
burn with the rest of us
and rise again,
reborn as a dragon
to turn his enemies
to ash.
I slit his throat to make sure
that didn't happen.
That's where Ned Stark
found me.
If this is true...
why didn't you tell anyone?
Why didn't you tell
Lord Stark?
Stark?
You think
the honorable Ned Stark
wanted to hear my side?
He judged me guilty
the moment
he set eyes on me.
By what right
does the wolf
judge the lion?
- By what right?
- Help! Help!
The Kingslayer!
Jaime.
My name is Jaime.
Onion Knight.
Ser Onion Knight.
Princess?
Gods, what are you doing here?
- Shh, you'll wake Bert.
- Bert?
He's the fat one.
He's on guard duty tonight.
He likes to drink wine
and sleep a lot.
Go back to your room.
You're not supposed to be here.
- If your father knew--
- He said you were a traitor.
Are you?
I am, child.
I disobeyed my king,
your father,
and now I'm paying
the price.
I don't care.
You're my friend.
You must get bored
down here.
I brought you
something to read.
It's about Aegon
and his dragons.
Aegon used to live here.
Did you know that?
- And the Targaryens built this castle.
- Aye.
- So they did.
- You can hide the book under your cloak.
It's a good one.
I'll bring you more.
Thank you, my lady.
I'm sure it's a fine book,
but it's wasted on me.
Take it.
I have more.
My lady, I can't read
the words.
You can't?
I'll teach you. I'll come when
Bert's on duty and teach you.
- No. No. No.
- It's easy. It'll be fun.
- Go. We can't.
- Why not?
What will they do,
lock us in cells?
I wouldn't know
where to start.
At the beginning.
This word is Aegon.
When you see A, E, and G
together like that,
it sounds like egg.
And the title
of the whole book
is "An History
of Aegon the Conqueror
and His Conquest
of Westeros."
It was a bitch
of a siege.
Mm, you were first
through the breach at Pyke?
The second.
Thoros of Myr went in alone,
waving that
flaming sword of his.
Thoros of Myr.
Bloody madman.
Robert knighted you
after the battle?
Proudest moment
of my life.
One knee in the dust,
the king's sword on my shoulder,
listening to the words.
"In the name of the Warrior,
I charge you to be brave."
All I could think of
was how badly I had to piss.
In full plate metal
for 16 hours.
Never occurred to me
till the fighting was over.
I was very nearly the first man
knighted to piss on the king's boots.
Robert would have
laughed.
He was a good man,
a great warrior.
And a terrible king.
I burned away my years
fighting for terrible kings.
- You swore an oath.
- Yes.
And a man of honor
keeps his vows,
even if he's serving
a drunk or a lunatic.
Just once in my life
before it's over,
I want to know what it's like
to serve with pride,
to fight for someone
I believe in.
Do you believe in her?
With all my heart.
These are the ones?
Yes, khaleesi.
The officers.
All Unsullied boys
are given new names
when they are cut--
Grey Worm, Red Flea,
Black Rat.
Names that remind them
what they are--
vermin.
King Robert
wanted her dead.
Of course
he wanted her dead.
She's a Targaryen.
The last Targaryen.
I suppose no one on the small
council could speak sense to him.
- I didn't sit on the small council.
- No?
Doesn't the Lord Commander
of the Kingsguard traditionally--
Traditionally, yes,
but I killed a dozen
of Robert's friends
during his rebellion.
He didn't want advice
on how to govern
from a man who had fought
for the Mad King.
Can't say
I minded much.
I always hated
the politics.
Yeah, I imagine
I would, too.
Hours spent jabbering
about backstabbings
- and betrayals the world over.
- Mm-hmm.
Still, she'll have
to wade through that muck
if she wants to rule
the Seven Kingdoms.
She'll have good men
around her to advise her,
men with experience.
Which men do you
have in mind?
Forgive me, Ser Jorah,
for what I'm about to say,
but your reputation in Westeros
has suffered over the years.
It suffered for a reason.
I sold men into slavery.
I don't know
if your presence by her side
will help our cause
when we go home.
Our cause?
Forgive me, Ser Barristan,
but I was busy
defending the khaleesi against
King Robert's assassins
while you were still
bowing to the man.
We both want her to rule.
Am I wrong?
You only joined us
a few days ago.
I can't speak
to your intentions.
If we're truly
her loyal servants,
we will do whatever
needs to be done,
no matter the cost,
no matter our pride.
You're not
Lord Commander here.
You're just another exile.
And I take my orders
from the queen.
- Come to bed.
- You were right.
The Karstarks are gone.
Almost half our forces.
Tywin Lannister knows what he
needs to do to make us unravel.
Nothing.
Only wait.
Don't let him.
What can I do?
Attack King's Landing?
There's nothing
he'd like better.
He'd crush us
in a day.
We could ride north.
Take your land back
from the Greyjoys.
- Wait out the winter.
- Winter could last five years.
Once my bannermen
are home again,
sitting by the fire,
surrounded by their families,
warm and safe,
they'll never ride south again.
When I gathered
my lords together,
we had a purpose,
a mission.
Now we're like a band
of bickering children.
Give them a new purpose.
What?
Oh, I don't know.
I don't even know
where Winterfell is.
Here.
And we're here.
King's Landing--
What is it?
I can't force them
to meet us in the field
and I can't attack them
where they're strongest,
but I can attack them
where they're not.
And Casterly Rock
can't run away.
I'm going to take
their home away from them.
Can you do it?
I need men to replace the Karstarks
who marched home.
There is only one person
in this kingdom
with that kind of army who hasn't
already sided with the Lannisters.
The man whose daughter
I was supposed to marry--
Walder Frey.
He's such
a splendid fighter.
Do you have any idea
when we might...
I'll plant the seed
as soon as Joffrey and I are married.
It should grow quickly.
Joffrey won't let me leave.
He's got too many reasons
to keep me here.
And only one
to let you go.
Because it will
please me.
Squire!
Well fought, ser.
That was no fight.
I don't know you.
Olyver,
if it please you.
I should like to see you spar with
a proper partner, ser.
How did you know?
Know what?
That I wanted to.
My lord...
I'll have you know
I'm to be married soon
and even my intended
hasn't the slightest notion.
They rarely do,
in my experience.
You have a good deal
of experience, do you?
With the husbands.
That didn't take long.
Well, it took long enough.
It seems our Knight of Flowers
is engaged to be wed.
Is he?
And...
who's the lucky girl?
She may not be the grandest
ship in the world
or the fastest,
but she's mine.
I've always wanted a ship.
Now I want a dozen.
- Strange, isn't it?
- What is?
It doesn't matter
what we want,
once we get it,
then we want
something else.
Your hair is different.
Is it?
Lady Margaery
wears it that way.
Many ladies
wear it this way.
I have good news.
I'll be leaving
the city soon.
You still want me
to come with you?
It's not a question
of what I want.
It's what you want.
You want to go home,
don't you?
Of course.
More than anything.
But maybe it would
be better to wait.
I've been thinking
how dangerous it would be.
Not just for me,
but for you.
You've been so kind.
I'd feel terrible if anything
happened to you.
I can't tell you
how touched I am
by your concern
for my welfare.
I hope you know that
I'm your friend, Sansa.
Your true friend.
I do, Lord Baelish.
- Petyr.
If you wish to stay,
then of course
you will stay.
We'll speak again
when I return.
You're late.
What's she doing here?
Our business
concerns her, too.
Sit.
You'll be pleased to learn
that after one conversation
with Olenna Tyrell,
I've saved the crown
hundreds of thousands
on this wedding.
Never mind that now.
We have something
important to discuss.
I'm Master of Coin.
Saving money is important.
Stop that.
You're making me
uncomfortable.
Your sister has learned that
your new friends the Tyrells
are plotting to marry
Sansa Stark to Ser Loras.
Very well.
She's a lovely girl.
Missing some of Loras'
favorite bits,
but I'm sure
they'll make do.
- Your jokes are not appreciated.
- It wasn't my best, but--
I bring them into the royal fold
and this is how they repay me,
by trying to steal the key to
the North out from under me.
Sansa is the key
to the North?
I seem to remember
she has an older brother.
The Karstarks
have marched home.
The young wolf has lost half his army.
His days are numbered.
Theon Greyjoy murdered
both his brothers.
That makes Sansa Stark
the heir to Winterfell.
And I am not about
to hand her over to the Tyrells.
The Tyrell army is helping
us to win this war.
Do you really think
it's wise to refuse them?
There's nothing to refuse.
This is a plot.
Plots are not
public knowledge.
And the Tyrells
won't carry this one out
until after
Joffrey's wedding.
We need to act first
and kill this union in its crib.
And how do we do that?
We find Sansa Stark
a different husband.
- Wonderful.
- Yes, it is.
You can't mean it.
I can and I do.
Joffrey has made this
poor girl's life miserable
since the day he took
her father's head.
Now she's finally free of
him and you give her to me?
That's cruel even for you.
Do you intend
on mistreating her?
The girl's happiness
is not my concern,
- nor should it be yours.
- She's a child!
She's flowered, I assure you.
She and I have discussed it at length.
There, you see? You will wed her,
bed her, and put a child in her.
- Surely you're capable of that.
- And if I refuse?
You wanted to be rewarded
for your valor in battle.
Sansa Stark is a finer reward than
you could ever dare hope for.
And it is past time
you were wed.
I was wed.
Or don't you remember?
Only too well.
You should be thanking
the gods for this.
This is more
than you deserve.
Tyrion will do as he's bid.
As will you.
What do you mean?
You'll marry Ser Loras.
- I will not.
- The boy is heir to Highgarden.
Tyrion will secure the North,
you will secure the Reach.
- No, I won't do it.
- Yes, you will.
You're still fertile.
You need to marry again and breed.
I am Queen Regent,
not some broodmare.
You're my daughter!
You will do as I command
and you will marry
Loras Tyrell
and put an end
to the disgusting rumors
about you
once and for all.
Father, don't make me
do it again, please.
Not another word.
My children.
You've disgraced the Lannister
name for far too long.
♪ It's always summer ♪
♪ Under the sea ♪
♪ I know, I know ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ The birds have scales ♪
♪ And the fish take wing ♪
♪ I know, I know ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ The rain is dry ♪
♪ And snow falls up ♪
♪ I know, I know ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ The stones crack open ♪
♪ The water burns ♪
♪ The shadows come
to dance ♪
♪ My lord ♪
♪ The shadows come ♪
♪ To play ♪
♪ The shadows
come to dance ♪
♪ My lord ♪
♪ The shadows come ♪
♪ To stay. ♪
www.tvsubtitles.net