— ♪ — theme music playing — ♪ —
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
—=«O»=—
www.addic7ed.com
(cawing)
(dog barking)
— You’re wearing a black cloak again.
— I’ve been sent to negotiate with you.
— It appears my trusting nature got the better of me.
— It’s happened before.
— I was hoping your loyalty was real when
you pledged yourself to us, Jon Snow.
— Truly I was.
— The Halfhand ordered me to join your army
— and bring back whatever information
I could to Castle Black.
— He made me kill him so you’d trust me.
— I was loyal…
— to him and to my Night’s Watch vows.
— All your vows?
— She wasn’t enough to turn you, eh?
— Were you enough to turn her?
— She put three arrows in me
— when I escaped.
— Did you see her again at Castle Black?
— Yes.
— And?
— She’s dead.
— Your doing?
— No.
— We’ll drink to her.
— Of all the ways I’d kill you,
— poison would be the last.
— Ygritte.
— (coughs)
— That’s not wine.
— No, it’s a proper northern drink, Jon Snow.
— You did well. Fought hard.
— Killed some of our strongest men.
— One of our giants went into your tunnel
— and never came out again.
— Mag the Mighty.
— He’s dead.
— He killed my friend Grenn.
— He was their king.
— The last of a bloodline that stretches back
— before the First Men.
— Grenn came from a farm.
— Mag and Grenn.
— Grenn and Mag.
— Kullback, could I trouble you for something to eat?
— I don’t imagine our guest has eaten anything
— for quite some time.
— So, you’re here to strike a bargain?
— Turn your army around and go home.
— You know I know you’re low on arrows,
— you’re low on oil, you’re low on men.
— How many are left, 50?
— I told Tormund and Orell.
— We have more than 1,000 men.
— I showed you everything I had.
— The whole army, 100,000 strong.
— And what did you do? You fired
on us with everything you had.
— It wasn’t much. As soon as I saw that,
— I sent 400 men to climb the Wall,
— an unmanned stretch five miles west of here.
— A lot of them will die climbing,
— but most of them will be over by the end of the day.
— It’s me being honest with you, Jon Snow,
— which is more than you’ve ever done for me.
— My people have bled enough.
— We’re not here to conquer.
— We’re here to hide behind your Wall.
— Just like you. We need your tunnel.
— Now we both know that winter is coming.
— And if my people aren’t south of
the Wall when it comes in earnest,
— we’ll all end up worse than dead.
— You want to strike a bargain with me?
— Here’s the bargain.
— You go back, you open the gates to us,
— and I swear to you that no one else will die.
— Refuse,
— and we’ll kill every last man at Castle Black.
— Ah!
— Oh, that’s why you’re here.
— I reckon you could do it before
any of them could stop you.
— They’d kill you, of course.
— They’d kill you slow.
— But you knew that when you came in here.
— Are you capable of that, Jon Snow?
— Killing a man in his own tent
when he’s just offered you peace?
— Is that what the Night’s Watch is?
— Is that what you are?
—  (horn blows)
— Man: Riders coming!
— Are you attacking us?
— No.
— It’s like you said, we don’t have the men.
—  (horn blowing)
—  (dogs barking)
(men shouting)
(horse whinnies)
— Hold! To me! To me!
(men shouting)
— Stand down!
— I said my people have bled enough
— and I meant it.
(shouting)
Man: — Round them up.
— Stay with the horses.
— You’re the King-beyond-the-Wall?
— Do you know who I am?
— Never had the pleasure.
— This is Stannis Baratheon,
— the one true king of the Seven Kingdoms.
— We’re not in the Seven Kingdoms and
you’re not dressed for this weather.
— It is customary to kneel when surrendering to a king.
— We do not kneel.
— I’ll have thousands of your men in chains by nightfall,
— have nowhere to put them, have nothing to feed them.
— I’m not here to slaughter beat dogs.
— Their fate depends on their king.
— All the same, we do not kneel.
— Take these men away.
— What’s a man of the Night’s
Watch doing in a wildling camp?
— I was sent to discuss terms
with the King-beyond-the-Wall.
— You’re speaking to the one true king, boy.
— You will address him as Your Grace.
— I know he’s the king. My father died for him.
— My name is Jon Snow, Your Grace.
— I’m Ned Stark’s son.
— Your father was an honorable man.
— He was, Your Grace.
— What do you think he’d have done with him?
— I was this man’s prisoner once.
— He could have tortured me. He could have killed me.
— But he spared my life.
— I think my father would have taken him prisoner,
— listened to what he had to say.
— Very well, then. Take him.
— Your Grace.
— If my father had seen the things that I’ve seen,
— he’d also tell you to burn the dead before nightfall.
— All of them.
(flies buzzing)
— I would suggest milk of the poppy
— to ease his pain, but he is completely insensate.
— Bloody Martells.
— The cause appears to be manticore venom.
— It is. The Death’s Head manticore.
— Yes, I’ve read a great deal about it.
— It’s a horrible poison.
— Usually Mantari in origin.
— Oh! Yes, yes.
— There’s nothing to be done.
— Yes, there is.
— May I ask what you think you’re doing?
— Saving him.
— Your Grace, I wish it were otherwise,
— but Ser Gregor is beyond saving.
— Well, well beyond.
— This man is not even a maester,
— let alone Grand Maester.
— That’s for the best.
— No maester knows how to save him.
— That is exactly the sort of arrogance
— that had him expelled from the Citadel, Your Grace.
— His curiosity was deemed dangerous and unnatural.
— Rightly so, in my opinion.
— You’re dismissed, Grand Maester.
— But, Your Grace, this is my laboratory.
— Not anymore.
Pycelle: — But I…
(scoffs)
(door opens)
— You can save him?
— Difficult to say, Your Grace.
— But if my past work is any guide…
(door slams)
— …we stand a chance.
— Do everything you can.
— Come to me for anything you need.
— Thank you, Your Grace.
— You should know,
— the process may change him…
— somewhat.
— Will it weaken him?
— Oh, no.
— Very well, then.
Tywin: — Not another word.
— We’ve been over this. The matter’s closed.
— I’m opening it again.
— You were betrothed to Loras Tyrell.
— You’re still betrothed to Loras Tyrell.
— And you will marry Loras Tyrell
— as soon as Tommen marries Margaery.
— I will not.
— Jaime cannot marry or inherit lands.
— Tyrion’s sentence will be carried out tomorrow.
— You have on several occasions made great claims
— about your commitment to this family’s future.
— Your role in that future
— is more vital now than it ever was.
— I don’t care.
— I will stay in King’s Landing where
I belong with my son the king.
— When you were nine years old,
I was called to the capital.
— I decided to take your
brother with me and not you.
— You insisted that you would
not be left at Casterly Rock
— under any circumstances. And if you recall–
— I’m not interested in hearing
another one of your smug stories
— about the time you won.
— This isn’t going to be one of those times.
— Do you think you’ll be the first person
— dragged into a sept to be married against her will?
— When you marched into the throne room to tell me
— we’d won the Battle of Blackwater… Do you remember?
— I was sitting on the Iron Throne with Tommen.
— I was about to give him essence of nightshade.
— That’s how far I was willing to go when I thought
— someone awful had come to take my son away.
— Someone awful is coming to take him away.
— No.
— Joffrey is dead.
— Myrcella’s been sold like livestock.
— And now you want to ship me off
to Highgarden and steal my boy.
— My last boy.
— Margaery will dig her claws in,
— you will dig your claws in
and you’ll fight over him
— like beasts until you rip him apart.
— I will burn our house to the
ground before I let that happen.
— And how will you do that?
— I’ll tell everyone the truth.
— What truth would that be?
— You don’t know, do you?
— You never believed it.
— How is that possible?
— What am I saying? Of course it’s possible.
— How can someone so consumed by the idea of his family
— have any conception what his actual family was doing?
— We were right there in front
of you and you didn’t see us.
— One look in the past 20 years,
— one real look at your own children
and you would have known.
— Known what?
— Everything they say is true.
— About Jaime and me.
— No.
— Your legacy is a lie.
— No, no, no, no.
— I don’t believe you.
— Yes, you do.
— Jaime.
— You won.
— One fewer brother. Must be proud of yourself.
— There’s really nothing you wouldn’t do, is there?
— For my family, no, nothing.
— I would do things for my
family you couldn’t imagine.
— Tyrion is your family.
— He’s not.
— You don’t get to choose.
— I do. So do you.
— You can choose the creature that killed
our mother to come into this world–
— Are you really mad enough to blame him for that?
— He didn’t decide to kill her. He was an infant.
— A disease doesn’t decide to kill you.
— All the same, you cut it out before it does.
— What do you decide? What do you choose?
— The things I did to get back to you,
— to endure all that, only to find you–
— I choose you.
— Those are words.
— Yes.
— Like the ones I just said to Father.
— I told him.
— Told him what?
— I told him about us.
— You told him?
— I told him I won’t marry Loras Tyrell.
— I told him I’m staying right here
with Tommen, with you.
— You think he’ll just accept that?
— Go and ask him.
— What did you say?
— I don’t want to talk about Tywin Lannister.
— I don’t choose Tywin Lannister.
— I don’t love Tywin Lannister.
— I love my brother.
— I love my lover.
— People will whisper, they’ll make their jokes.
— Let them.
— They’re all so small, I can’t even see them.
— I only see what matters.
— Someone will walk in.
— I don’t care.
—
— I can speak the common tongue if you wish.
— You speak it very well.
— Before you freed me, I belonged to Master Mighdal.
— I was tutor to his children.
— I taught them languages and history.
— They know a great deal about your family because of me.
— Little Calla is only seven,
— but she admires you very much.
— I hope I can prove worthy of her admiration.
— What can I do for you?
— When you took the city, the children begged me
— not to leave the house.
— But Master Mighdal and I agreed that I must.
— So I lost my home.
— Now I live on the streets.
— I have outfitted mess halls
— to feed all former slaves and barracks to shelter them.
— I do not mean to offend, Your Grace.
— I went to one of these places.
— The young prey on the old.
— Take what they want and beat us if we resist.
— My Unsullied will make them
safe again in short order,
— my friend, this I promise you.
— Even if they are safe, who would I be there?
— What purpose would I serve?
— With my master, I was a teacher.
— I had the respect and love of his children.
— What is it that you want from me?
— Your Grace, I ask you
— to let me sell myself back to Master Mighdal.
— You want to return to a man who owned you
— like a goat or a chair?
— Please, Your Grace.
— The young may rejoice in the new
world you have built for them,
— but for those of us too old to change,
— there is only fear and squalor.
— I am not alone.
— There are many outside waiting to beg the same of you.
— I did not take this city to preside
— over the injustice I fought to destroy.
— I took it to bring people freedom.
— But freedom means making your own choices.
— I will allow you to sign a
contract with your former master.
— It may not cover a period
lasting longer than a year.
— Thank you, Your Grace.
— Thank you.
— The masters will take advantage of this situation.
— The men serving them
— will be slaves in all but name.
— Approach, my friend.
—
(sobbing)
(speaking low Valyrian)
Missandei: — I have brought you–
— He came from the sky.
— The black one.
— The winged shadow.
— He came from the sky and…
— My girl.
— My little girl.
(sobbing)
Daenerys: — What was her name?
Missandei: — Zala, Your Grace.
— How old was she?
— Three.
—
(screeching)
(roaring)
Aemon: —  They came to us from
White Harbor and Barrowton,
— from Fairmarket and King’s Landing,
— from north and south,
— from east and west.
— They died protecting men, women, and children
— who will never know their names.
— It is for us to remember them.
— Our brothers,
— we shall never see their like again.
All: — And now their watch is ended.
Aemon: — And now their watch is ended.
— Your old blind man patched me up.
— Why?
— He’s sworn to treat all wounded men, friend or foe.
— You want me alive so you can torture me?
— No one’s gonna torture you.
— So how do we die? Hanging? Beheading?
— Drop us from the top of the Wall?
— I don’t know what happens to the prisoners.
— Who decides?
— I suppose Stannis does.
— He your king now?
— I don’t have a king.
— You spent too much time with us, Jon Snow.
— You can never be a kneeler again.
— We’re gonna burn the bodies of your dead.
— Do you want to say any words over them?
— Words? What kind of words?
— Funeral words. I don’t know how the free folk do it.
— Do what?
— Say farewell.
— The dead can’t hear us, boy.
— Snow.
— Did you love her?
— She loved you.
— She told you?
— No.
— All she ever talked about was killing you.
— That’s how I know.
— She belongs in the North.
— The real North.
— You understand me?
(wind howling)
(groaning)
— We can stop. We can rest.
— We’ll rest with the three-eyed raven.
— We’re not going to make it.
— We’re already here.
Bran: — Jojen.
— Jojen.
— Look, Jojen. Look.
(groaning)
— Jojen! Come on!
— Help them! Now!
Meera: — Hold on to me!
— Hang on!
— Hodor.
— Help them!
— (growling)
— Hodor!
— (screeching)
— (grunts)
— Hodor!
— (growling)
— Hodor. (whimpering)
— Hodor!
Jojen: — Bran!
— Save yourself, now!
— (grunting)
— (shouts)
Girl: —  Come with me, Brandon Stark.
— (gasping)
— He is lost.
— Come with me or die with him.
— Go with them.
— (ice bursting)
— (slices)
— (growling)
— They cannot follow us.
— The power that moves them is powerless here.
— Who are you?
— The First Men called us the children,
— but we were born long before them.
— Come, he waits for you.
— (crow caws)
— (caws)
— You’re the three-eyed raven?
— I’ve been many things.
— Now I am what you see.
— My brother, he led us to you and now he–
— He knew what would happen.
— From the moment he left,
— he knew and he went anyway.
— How do you know?
— I’ve been watching you.
— All of you.
— All of your lives.
— With 1,000 eyes and one.
— Now you’ve come to me at last,
— Brandon Stark.
— Though the hour is late.
— I didn’t want anyone to die for me.
— He died so you could find what you have lost.
— You’re going to help me walk again?
— You will never walk again.
— But you will fly.
— (bird squawks)
— Podrick.
— Where are the horses?
— I hobbled them last night.
— What sort of hobble?
— A figure eight like you taught me.
— If you did it like I taught you,
— then the horses would be here.
— Thieves, maybe?
— It’s at least 30 miles to the Eyrie from here.
— You’re carrying the saddlebags.
— (grunting)
— People coming.
— You can shit later. There’s people coming.
— Morning.
— I like your sword.
— Are we getting close to the Bloody Gate?
— About 10 more miles.
— Did you hear that, Podrick?
— Only 10 more miles to the Bloody Gate.
— Are you a knight?
— No.
— But you know how to use that sword?
— I do.
— Does it have a name?
— Oathkeeper.
— Mine’s Needle.
— Good name.
— Who taught you how to fight?
— My father.
— Mine never wanted to.
— Said fighting was for boys.
— Mine said the same.
— But I kept fighting the boys anyway.
— Kept losing.
— Finally my father said, «If you’re going to do it,
— you might as well
do it right.»
— Seven blessings.
— I’m Brienne of Tarth. This is Podrick Payne.
— You want something?
— That’s Sandor Clegane. The Hound.
— You’re Arya Stark.
— I asked if you wanted something.
— I swore to your mother I would bring you home to her.
— My mother’s dead.
— I know.
— I wish I could have been there to protect her.
— You’re not a northerner.
— No, but I swore a sacred vow to protect her.
— Why didn’t you?
— She commanded me to bring Jaime
Lannister back to King’s Landing.
— You’re paid by the Lannisters.
— You’re here for the bounty on me.
— I’m not paid by the Lannisters.
— No?
— Fancy sword you’ve got there.
— Where’d you get it?
— I’ve been looking at Lannister gold all my life.
— Go on, Brienne of fucking Tarth.
— Tell me that’s not Lannister gold.
— Jaime Lannister gave me this sword.
— The Bloody Gate is 10 miles.
— I swore to your mother by the old gods–
— I don’t care what you swore.
— Arya!
Hound: — You heard the girl.
— She’s not coming with you.
— She is.
— You’re not a good listener.
— That Valyrian steel?
— I always wanted some Valyrian steel.
— Come with me, Arya. I’ll take you to safety.
— Safety? Where the fuck’s that?
— Her aunt in the Eyrie is dead. Her mother’s dead.
— Her father’s dead. Her brother’s dead.
— Winterfell is a pile of rubble.
— There is no safety, you dumb bitch.
— You don’t know that by now,
— you’re the wrong one to watch over her.
— And that’s what you’re doing?
— Watching over her?
— Aye, that’s what I’m doing.
— (grunts)
— (panting)
— I have no wish to kill you, Ser.
— I’m not a knight.
— (grunts)
— (groans)
— (screams)
— (screaming)
— (groans)
— (shouting)
— Arya!
— Where is she?
Podrick: — She was just here.
— Why weren’t you watching her?
— I was watching you. I thought you might need some help.
— Which way, Pod? Which way did she go?
— I think that way.
Brienne: — Arya!
— Arya!
— (panting)
— You still here?
— (coughs)
— Big bitch saved you.
— I don’t need saving.
— No, not you. You’re a real killer.
— With your water dancing
— and your Needle.
— You gonna die?
— Unless there’s a maester hiding behind that rock,
— aye,
— I’m done.
— I’d skin you alive for wine.
— Fuck water.
— Killed by a woman.
— (chuckles)
— I bet you like that.
— Go on,
— go after her.
— She’ll help you.
— Going it alone,
— you won’t last a day out there.
— I’ll last longer than you.
— You remember where the heart is?
— Fuck it.
— I’m ready.
— Go on, girl.
— Another name off your list.
— You kept promising me.
— I cut down your butcher’s boy.
— The ginger.
— He was begging for mercy.
— «Please, Ser. Please don’t kill me.
— Please, please.»
— Bled all over my horse.
— Saddle stunk of butcher’s
boy for weeks.
— And your sister.
— Your pretty sister.
— I should have taken her.
— That night the Blackwater burned.
— I should have fucked her bloody.
— At least I’d have one happy memory.
— Do I have to beg you?
— Do it.
— Kill me.
— Kill me!
— (door opens)
— (door closes)
— (footsteps)
— Oh, get on with it, you son of a whore.
— Is that any way to speak about our mother?
— What are you doing?
— What do you think I’m doing?
— A galley’s waiting in the bay bound for the Free Cities.
— Who’s helping you?
— Varys.
— Varys?
– You have more friends than you thought.
— There’s a locked door at the top of the stairs.
— Knock on it twice, then twice again.
— Varys will open.
— I suppose this is good-bye, then.
— Farewell, little brother.
— Jaime.
— Thank you for my life.
— Quickly now.
— Tywin?
— My lion.
— (grunting)
— (choking)
— (grunts)
— (gasping)
— (whimpers)
— I’m sorry.
— (exhales)
— (crossbow lever dragging)
— (door creaks)
— Tyrion.
— Put down the crossbow.
— Who released you?
— Your brother, I expect.
— He always had a soft spot for you.
— Come, we’ll go and talk in my chambers.
— This is how you want to speak to me, hmm?
— Shaming your father has always given you pleasure.
— All my life
— you’ve wanted me dead.
— Yes.
— But you refused to die.
— I respect that.
— Even admire it.
— You fight for what’s yours.
— I’d never let them execute you.
— Is that what you fear?
— I’ll never let Ilyn Payne take your head.
— You’re a Lannister.
— You’re my son.
— I loved her.
— Who?
— Shae.
— Oh, Tyrion.
— Put down that crossbow.
— I murdered her.
— With my own hands.
— It doesn’t matter.
— Doesn’t matter?
— She was a whore.
— Say that word again…
— And what?
— You’ll kill your own father in the privy?
— No.
— You’re my son.
— Now, enough of this nonsense.
— I am your son and you sentenced me to die.
— You knew I didn’t poison Joffrey,
— but you sentenced me all the same.
— Why?
— Enough.
— We’ll go back to my chambers
— and speak with some dignity.
— I can’t go back there. She’s in there.
— You’re afraid of a dead whore?
— (groans)
— You shot me.
— You’re no son of mine.
— I am your son.
— I have always been your son.
— (groans)
— What have you done?
— Quickly.
— Trust me, my friend. I brought you this far.
— (bells tolling)
— I want to see the captain.
— You’re seeing him.
— I want to go north to the Wall.
— No, you don’t.
— I can pay.
— There is nothing in the North
but ice and war and pirates.
— I wouldn’t need a cabin. Please.
— I could work scrubbing the floors.
— I’m not going north, child. I’m going home.
— Where’s home?
— The Free City of Braavos.
— Wait. I have something else.
— More silver won’t make a difference.
— It’s not silver. It’s iron.
— This…
— How did you–
— Valar morghulis.
— Valar dohaeris.
— Of course, you shall have a cabin.
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
—=«O»=—
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net