Transcript by honeybunny & No1
www.addic7ed.com
- Valar morghulis.
- Valar dohaeris.
I've been sweeping this floor for days.
- Good.
- I didn't come here to sweep floors.
No? Why come than?
You said that I could be your apprentice.
You said you'd teach me
how to a Faceless Man.
A man teaches a girl.
Valar dohaeris.
All men must serve.
Faceless men, most of all.
I want to serve.
A girl wants to serve herself.
Here we serve the Many-Faced God,
to serve well.
- A girl must become no-one.
- Which one is the Many-Faced God?
I see the Stranger, I see the Drowned God,
- I see the Weirwood Face.
- There is only one god.
A girl knows his name.
And no man know his gift.
Where are they taking him?
Queen Margaery!
- I'm his, and he's mine.
- I'm hers, and she's mine.
- From this day until the end of my days.
- Did I hurt you?
- No. You were lovely.
- It all happened so fast.
- Yes.
I was scared maybe I hurt you,
it sounded like...
No, no, no...
you're very sweet.
The sweetest king who ever lived.
This is what I want to do all day,
every day for the rest of my life.
Wouldn't that be glorious?
Shouldn't we rest a little while?
Just to catch our breath,
there's no rush, is there?
Of course not.
Are you hungry?
Shall I have them bring you some cake
or pomegranate juice...?
No, I'm fine...
I just want you all to myself.
I want to know everything there is to know
about King Tommen First of His Name.
King Tommen...
it still sounds strange to me.
Does Queen Margaery sound strange to you?
- So strange. Husband.
- Wife.
Sometimes it feels odd.
I'm the king, I've married
the most beautiful woman in the world,
and it's all because my brother died.
I understand.
But it's no your fault,
you know that, don't you?
You mustn't feel guilty.
I don't feel guilty.
That's what's odd.
Do you like to sail?
- I love to sail.
- I do, too.
I think we're going to be very happy,
you and I.
I do, too.
Living in a tower so high,
it touches the clouds.
Of course my grandmother
couldn't wait to go home.
The capital is not for everyone, I suppose.
Does your mother like it here?
I don't think so.
She told me never to trust anyone
in King's Landing.
It's so wonderful to have her
watching over you.
A lioness guiding her cub.
Well, but I'm a man now.
You are.
And the king.
But you'll always be her baby-boy.
I suppose.
I adore how she has always been
so generous with me, so kind.
And the horror she's had to endure.
Losing her husband,
her eldest child and her father.
It's no wonder she's so protective of you.
She'll never let you out of her sight.
You're very much in love.
The first days of marriage
are often so blissful.
She's certainly very pretty, isn't she?
Like a doll, she smiles quite a lot.
Do you think she's intelligent?
I can't quite tell.
- Not that it matters.
- Do you ever miss Casterly Rock?
There's nothing for me in Casterly Rock.
That's where you grew up.
You always told me
that you liked the people there better.
You said that King's Landing
smelled of horse dung and sour milk.
- Why are we speaking of Casterly Rock?
- The way that you talked about it...
I always thought that you missed it.
- That you... That it was your real home.
- This is my real home now.
Where my family lives.
I want you to be happy, mother.
I know that.
- I know you do, my sweet boy.
- But wouldn't you be happier in Casterly Rock?
I said, "Darling, surely 4 times is enough,
are you trying to set a new record?"
And he said, "Well, what is the record?
I'm sure we can break it."
Mother.
Welcome.
Well don't you look lovely.
Marriage agrees with you.
Can we bring you anything to eat or drink?
I wish we had some wine for you.
It's a bit early in the day for us.
No, no, I...I can't stay.
I just wanted to let you know if...
there is ever anything I can do for you.
You are very sweet.
Tommen seems quite taken
with his new queen.
I absolutely adore him.
You raised a gallant young man.
- I'm forever grateful.
- Good.
Good.
I'm glad to hear you're happy.
Ecstatic. I really am.
Exhausted, to be honest, but
what can I expect, he is
half lion, half stag.
I'll leave you to it then.
Oh, forgive me, I haven't been at
Court for long, I get so confused.
What's the proper way to address you now?
Queen Mother or Dowager Queen?
There's no need for such formalities.
In any event, judging from
the King's enthusiasm,
the Queen Mother will be a
Queen Grandmother soon.
That'll be a lovely day.
Imagine the celebrations.
They'll ring the bells all day and night.
Remember.
Anything you need.
We can't hold the North with terror alone.
You can't hold the North if you
let these lesser lords insult us.
I sent you there to collect
taxes, not bodies.
Lord Cerwyn refused to pay.
He said the Warden of the
North will always be a Stark,
and he'd be damned if he
kissed a traitor's boot.
You left him no choice.
I flayed him living,
along with his wife and brother.
I made his son watch.
And?
The new Lord Cerwyn paid his taxes.
I have something important to tell you.
Stop eating and listen.
We don't have enough men to hold the North
if the other Houses rise up against us.
Do you understand that?
Our pact with the Lannisters...
I had a pact with Tywin Lannister.
Tywin Lannister is dead.
The remaining Lannisters are a thousand
miles away dealing with that fact.
They've never once in the
history of the Seven Kingdoms
sent their army this far north.
If you think they will for us,
you're a fool.
We become a great House by entering
in alliances with other Houses,
and parleying those alliances
into greater power.
Now the best way to forge
a lasting alliance
isn't by peeling a man's skin off,
the best way is marriage.
Now that you're a Bolton by royal decree,
it's time you married a suitable bride.
And as it happens,
I found the perfect girl to
solidify our hold in the North.
- That's Moat Cailin.
- Yes.
A bit shabby, isn't it?
You've been here before.
On our way down to King's Landing,
with my father and Arya and...
- Where are you taking me?
- Home.
The Boltons have Winterfell.
The marriage proposal...It wasn't for you?
No.
Roose Bolton murdered my brother.
He betrayed my family!
He did.
He serves the Lannisters.
- For now.
- I won't go.
- Winterfell is your home.
- Not anymore.
Always. You're a Stark.
Dyeing your hair doesn't change that.
You're Sansa Stark.
The eldest surviving child
of Ned and Catelyn Stark.
Your place is in the North.
I can't marry him.
You can't make me.
He's a traitor.
A murderer.
You're not marrying Roose Bolton.
No, you'll be marrying his son and heir,
Ramsay.
- One day he'll be Warden of the North and...
- No!
- Sansa...
- No, you can't make me.
I will starve myself. I will
die before I have to go there.
I won't force you to do anything.
Don't you know by now how
much I care for you?
Say the word and we turn the
horses round, but listen to me.
Listen.
You've been running all your life.
Terrible things happened to
your family and you weep.
You sit alone in a dark room,
mourning their fates.
You've been a bystander to tragedy from
the day they executed your father.
Stop being a bystander, you hear me?
Stop running.
There's no justice in the world.
Not unless we make it.
You loved your family.
Avenge them.
How do we get through there?
We don't.
We go around.
It sets miles out of the way.
- We'll lose sight of them.
- Doesn't matter.
I know where they're going.
Don't you get a bit old for a squire?
How did you end up squiring for the Imp?
He hates that nickname.
Well, he's not here to
complain about it, is he?
I squired for a knight name Ser Lorimer
during the War of the Five Kings.
One night,
he had a bit too much to drink.
And he was famished, so he borrowed a ham.
- He borrowed it?
- He wasn't a thief.
He was drunk and hungry
and he wasn't thinking.
I was drunk too.
He gave me half the ham.
Next morning,
one of the guards saw him passed out,
under a wagon, with the ham
bone still in his hand.
They hanged the man after noon.
They tied the noose for me too,
but Lord Tywin heard my
family name was Payne,
so he pardoned me,
and sent me to King's Landing
to squire for his son.
Punishment?
- For both of you.
- It didn't seem that way.
Lord Tyrion was always very good to me.
I guess all of your lords
were very kind to you.
All except me.
Sorry you have to squire
such a nasty person.
I'm not sorry. You're the
best fighter I've ever seen.
You beat The Hound.
I'm proud to be your squire.
I'm sorry I'm always snapping at you.
If you wouldn't snap at me
I wouldn't learn anything.
You want to be a knight, Pod?
Yes.
Starting tomorrow, we'll train
with the sword twice a day,
before we ride in the morning and
after we camp for the evening.
And I'm going to show you
how to ride properly.
Thank you.
I can't knight you,
but I can teach you how to fight.
I suppose that's more important.
You weren't a knight, but
you were a Kingsguard to Renly Baratheon,
weren't you?
I was.
Lord Tyrion said he was a good man.
He was.
But how did you end up serving Renly?
When I was a girl,
my father held a ball.
I'm his only living child, so he wants
to make a good match for me.
He invited dozens of young lords to Tarth.
I didn't want to go, but he dragged me
to the ballroom.
And it was wonderful.
None of the boys noticed
how mulish and tall I was.
The shaft each other and threatened to duel
if they thought it was their turn to dance.
Whispered in my ear
how they wanted to marry me and take me
back to their castles.
My father smiled at me and I smiled at him.
I'd never been so happy.
Till I saw a few of the boys sniggering.
And then they all started to laugh, they
couldn't keep the game going any longer.
They were toying with me.
Brienne the Beauty, they called me.
Great joke.
And I realized I was the
ugliest girl alive.
A great lumbering beast.
I tried to run away, but Renly Baratheon
took me in his arms.
Don't let them see your tears, he told me.
The nasty little shits,
nasty little shits aren't worth
crying over.
He danced with me and none of the
other boys could say a word.
And he was the king's brother after all.
But...wasn't he...
Lord Tyrion said he was...
Yes, Pod, he liked men,
I'm not an idiot.
He didn't love me, he didn't want me,
he danced with me because he was kind
and he wouldn't see me hurt.
He saved me from being a joke.
From that day
until his last day.
And I couldn't save him in return.
Nothing's more hateful than failing
to protect the one you love.
One day, I will avenge King Renly.
But you said a shadow murdered him.
How do you fight a shadow?
A shadow with the face
of Stannis Baratheon.
I know it was Stannis.
I know it in my heart.
Stannis is a man, not a shadow.
And a man...
can be killed.
- Lord Commander.
- Your Grace.
I'd like to speak alone.
Ollie is my steward now, as I was
Lord Commander Mormont's.
I want him to attend my meetings,
to learn from men with experience.
One day, he might command.
Very well. Have you considered my offer?
I have.
And I thank you for it.
You do me great honor.
All my life I wanted to be Jon Stark.
Say the word and you will be.
But I have to refuse you.
I'm Lord Commander of the Night's Watch.
My place is here.
I'm giving you a chance
to avenge your family.
Take back the castle where you grew up.
To rule the North.
I wish I could fight beside you.
Believe me, I do.
But I swore a sacred vow at the Godswood.
I pledged my life to the Night's Watch.
You're as stubborn as your father.
And as honorable.
I can imagine no higher praise.
I didn't mean it as praise.
Honor got your father killed.
But if your mind is made up,
I won't try to persuade you.
Can I ask Your Grace
how long you plan to stay
at Castle Black?
Are you bored of us already?
You saved us from Mance Rayder's army.
We will never forget that.
But it's a question of survival.
Night's Watch can't continue to feed your men
and the wildling prisoners indefinitely.
Mm, winter is coming.
I know it.
We march on Winterfell within a fortnight.
Before the snows trap us here.
And the wildlings?
They'd rather burn than fight for me,
so be it.
I leave their fate to you.
You could execute them,
that's the safest course.
Or you could see if this Tormund fellow
is more willing
to compromise than Mance ever was.
I assume the brothers of the Night's Watch
would rather see the wildlings dead.
Most of the brothers, yes.
There's little love for the free folk here.
You're Lord Commander.
Your decision.
You have many enemies in Castle Black.
Have you considered sending
Alliser Thorne elsewhere?
Give him command of Eastwach-by-the-Sea.
I heard it was best to
keep your enemies close.
Whoever said that didn't have many enemies.
He sees something in you.
Might not be apparent from his tone,
but it's the truth. He believes in you.
I'm sorry I disappointed him.
The king is a complicated man.
But he wants what's right
for the Seven Kingdoms.
As long as he's ruling them.
He's the one true king.
He has the blood right to that throne.
I sworn to stay clear of the politics
of the Seven Kingdoms.
Have you now?
How does the Night's Watch vow go again?
I bet you've got it memorized
since you got here.
Night gathers and now my watch begins...
Not that bit, the bit at the end.
I'm the sword in the darkness,
the watcher on the walls,
the shield that guards the realm of men.
- I pledge my life...
- Okay, that's enough.
Shield that guards the realm of men.
That's what you swore to be.
Now I'm not a learned man,
the best way of helping the most people
might not be sitting
in a frozen castle at
the edge of the world.
It just might mean wading in the muck
and getting your boots dirty
and doing what needs to be done.
And what needs to be done?
As long as the Boltons rule the North,
the North will suffer.
Just one man's opinion.
What do you want?
Who are you?
What?
You, who walk in here
with a coin you never earned,
whose value you do not respect.
Who are you?
No one. Ou! Cunt!
A lie, a sad little lie.
- Who are you?
- I told you, I'm no...
Do that again and...
Who are you?
You're about to find out.
What are you doing?
We're only playing.
The game of faces.
That girl is not ready.
Clearly not.
I am ready.
For what?
For every you want
to be a Faceless Man.
To be no one.
Whose sword is that?
It belongs to Arya Stark.
Arya Stark's sword, Arya Stark's clothes,
Arya Stark's stolen silver.
A man wonders
how is it that no one
came to be surrounded
by Arya Stark's things?
What do you do with them
after you wash them?
Open gates!
Hold up!
Lady Sansa, welcome.
Lord Bolton.
May I introduce my son, Ramsay Bolton?
It's an honor to meet you.
I'll bring you a bowl of hot water.
You must want to wash.
Thank you.
Welcome home, Lady Stark.
The North remembers.
Sam.
Maester Aemon?
He apologizes for not being here.
He's not feeling well.
Take good care of him.
I will drink it then.
He'll lose.
As you all know too well,
it's long past time to
dig a new latrine pit.
First Builder Yarwyck and I have decided
to appoint
a latrine captain to
oversee this crucial task.
Brian.
It seems like a good job for a ginger.
Ser Alliser.
You have more experience
than any other ranger at Castle Black.
You proved your valour many times over
by defending the Wall
from the wildling attack.
I name you First Ranger.
Lord Janos.
I'm giving you command of Greyguard.
Greyguard is a ruin.
Yes, the fort is in a sorry state.
Restore it as best you can.
First Builder Yarwyck can spare...
I was charged with the defense of
King's Landing
when you were soiling
your swaddling clothes.
Keep your ruin.
Alright, alright.
Enough of that.
You mistake me, my Lord.
That was a command, not an offer.
Pack your arms and armour,
say your farewells,
and ride for Greyguard.
I will not go meekly off to freeze and die.
Give it to one of the fools
who cast a stone for you.
I will not have it.
Did you hear me, boy?
I will not have it!
You refusing to obey my order?
You can stick your order
up your bastard arse.
Take Lord Janos outside.
Ollie, bring me my sword.
You cannot do this!
Get your hands off me!
You're scum! All of you!
The boy thinks he can frighten me?
He's mistaken, yes, very mistaken.
A disgrace!
I have friends, important friends
in the capital!
You'll see!
If you have any last words, my Lord...
now is the time.
I was wrong. You're the Lord Commander!
We all serve you. I'm sorry. Not only
for this, for all I've done and said.
I was wrong!
My Lord, please, mercy! Mercy!
I'll go! I will!
Please.
I'm afraid.
I've always been afraid.
You have served us well, my son.
Thank you, Father!
Which of the Seven will you worship today?
The Maiden...where is the Maiden?
And the Stranger.
- Two is extra, you realize...
- Yes, yes.
What are you doing?
This establishment belong to
Lord Petyr Baelish. You can't...
You have profaned our Faith.
The Faith of our fathers and forefathers.
I am the High Septon of the...
You are a sinner.
And you shall be punished.
Sinner! Sinner!
Sinner! Repent!
Sinner! Sinner! Sinner!
Sinner! Shame on you!
Sinner!
Your Grace, Grandmaester,
Lord Tyrell...
Uh, it doesn't matter.
As the High Septon of
the Faith of the Seven
I give voice to the will of the Gods
and I am their foremost
servant in this world.
An insult to me is an insult to the Gods.
An assault on my person
is an assault on our very religion.
You were assaulted?
I was.
By those fanatics who
call themselves sparrows.
And they humiliated me, they...
they beat me, they left me naked
and bleeding on the cobblestones.
I am lucky to be alive.
I heard this all began in
Littlefinger's brothel.
High Septon, this is a rather
shocking thing to hear.
I tend to both the highest born
and the lowliest amongst us.
Even prostitutes may earn
the mercy of the Mother.
So you were administering to the
needs of these devout prostitutes?
A man's private affairs
ought to stay private.
What do you want from us, High Septon?
Justice!
I ask that you protect our Faith
by arresting these criminals
and throw them in the black cells.
I ask that you execute their leader,
the so-called High Sparrow.
He's a threat to everything we hold sacred.
- If he goes unpunished...
- And where do I find this man?
This High Sparrow?
I don't think this is a
good idea, Your Grace.
Nonsense, Ser Meryn.
These are deeply religious people.
Where can I find the High Sparrow?
Seven blessings...
Thank the Gods.
Just a little more.
Thank you for the soup.
The young man said I would find the
High Sparrow back here. Where is he?
High Sparrow?
Sounds ridiculous, doesn't it?
Like Lord Duckling, or King Turtle.
So, it's meant to...
We're often stuck with the
names our enemies give to us.
The notion that we are all
equal in the eyes of Seven
doesn't sit well with some
so they belittle me.
- Seven blessings to you.
- Seven blessings to you, my dear.
It's only a name, quite
an easy burden to wear.
Far easier than hers.
Why no shoes?
Because I gave them away to
someone who needed them more.
We all do that.
It stops us from forgetting
who we really are.
Is that why you came to King's Landing?
To remind everyone?
Everyone? I have a hard
time reminding myself.
Well, I tell them no one's special.
They think I'm special for telling them so.
Perhaps they're right.
It would be comforting to
believe that, wouldn't it?
The Gods sent you here to tempt me?
I hope not.
I'd assumed
you'd only come here to arrest me.
For that incident with the High Septon.
An unacceptable way to treat
the chosen representative
of the Gods in this
world, wouldn't you say?
Hypocrisy is a boil.
Lancing a boil is never pleasant.
Although, they could have been more careful
with the blade.
The High Septon came to speak to me today.
He doesn't want me to arrest you,
he wants me to execute you.
I wouldn't presume to know
your thoughts on the matter.
My thoughts on the matter
align with your own.
The High Septon's behaviour was corosive,
as was his attitude.
Having a man like that reside in the Sept
eats away the Faith from the inside.
So now he resides in the Red
Keep's dungeons instead.
The Faith and the Crown are the two
pillars that hold up this world.
If one collapses, so does the other.
You must do everything necessary
to protect one another.
Your Grace.
Send a message to Littlefinger
in the Eyrie or wherever
he's slythering about.
At once, Your Grace.
- How's your work coming along?
- Very well.
- You've made progress?
- More than I've expected.
Still a way to go, but...
Very good. I'll leave you to it then.
Make sure Littlefinger is clear on
the meaning of the word "immediate".
Shh...
Easy, friend.
Come on, children.
She really is lovely.
I hope I can make her happy.
I hope so too.
I've become quite fond of Lady Sansa
during our travels together.
She suffered enough.
I'll never hurt her.
You have my word.
I've heard very little about you.
Which makes you quite a rare thing,
as lords go.
I haven't been a lord very long.
- I was a bastard.
- And you're not anymore.
Allow me a moment alone with
Lord Baelish.
Yes, father.
And thank you, Lord Baelish.
I'm forever in your debt.
He seems pleased.
Shouldn't he be?
I assure you she's still a virgin.
Tyrion never consumated the marriage. By
the law of the land, she's no man's wife.
Inspect her, if you must.
I leave that to the brothel keeper.
It's her name I need, not her virtue.
I have delivered everything I've promised.
And you prepared for the consequences.
When the Lannisters hear I've
wed Sansa Stark to Ramsay.
The Lannister name doesn't
mean what it once did.
Tywin is dead.
He kept his house in power
through sheer will.
Without him,
Jaime has one hand and no allies,
Tommen is a soft boy,
not a king to fear.
The Queen will be enraged.
Queen Margaery adores Sansa.
Cersei is Queen Mother,
a title whose importance
wanes with each passing day.
You noticed, still as friends
men in important places,
whom she can ask for favours.
A message for you,
from Cersei Lannister.
A rider arrived from Eyrie,
shortly before dawn.
Apparently, she thinks
you're still in the Vale.
A message for me, you say.
Strange that the seal is broken.
I'm sure you understand my
position, Lord Baelish.
If you received word in the night
from the Queen Mother,
it does make me question our new alliance.
Lannisters made you one of
the great lords of Westeros.
Yet, here you are in the North,
undermining them.
Why gamble with your position?
Every ambitious move is a gamble.
You gambled when you drove a dagger
into Robb Stark's heart.
It appears that your gamble paid off.
You're Warden of the North.
I had Tywin Lannister backing.
Who supports me now? You?
The Eyrie is mine.
The last time the lords of the Eyrie formed
an alliance with the lords of the North,
they brought down the greatest dynasty
this world has ever known.
I'd like to borrow one of your birds.
Cersei will expect a reply.
I'd like to read the reply.
I have to get out of this wheelhouse.
Volantis is a large city.
The likelihood of you being spotted here
increases a hundred fold.
I have to get out of this wheelhouse.
I'm not sure how many new ways
I can find of saying this.
I will not be of any use
to Daenerys Targaryen
if I lose my mind.
I can't remember the last
face I saw that wasn't yours.
It's a perfectly good face.
I'm losing my mind.
If anyone recognizes you,
you'll lose more than...
Look, we are thousands
of miles from Westeros.
What am I?
One more drunk dwarf.
We have to go now. Come on.
Hold it, hold it!
- Slaves.
- Yes.
The Volantene masters are very organized.
Flies for dung shovelers.
Hammers for builders.
Tears for whores.
Lest they forget.
_
We should keep moving.
The only red priest we had in
King's Landing was Thoros of Myr.
This one's much better looking.
_
Stone men.
Good luck stopping this spread
of grayscale with prayer.
You'd have better luck
dancing away the plague.
_
We're going to meet the Saviour.
You should have told me.
Who doesn't want to meet the Saviour?
Come on.
Let's find a brothel.
_
It's even better luck
to suck a dwarf's cock.
See? We blend right in.
Just two more travellers, mad with lust.
Thank you.
Curious hair.
The Mother of Dragons.
It appears you're not the
only Targaryen supporter.
Someone who inspires priests and
whores is worth taking seriously.
What makes you worth that much?
The magic.
Well, she's taken.
Where're you going?
I need to speak to someone with hair.
- Hello?
- Hello.
- You've got no drink.
- You've got no money.
Do I look like a man without money?
Never trust looks.
Until quite recently, I was one
of the richest men in the world.
But who needs wealth when
you can make a woman laugh?
I always pay my debts,
I'm well known for it.
You like her?
They all like her.
They all want to fuck a queen.
- Because they never met a queen.
- You're just saying that.
You know how to spot a liar.
If I could pick any girl here,
I would pick you.
Why?
Because you have a skeptical mind.
Alright, then. I'm warning you.
You're gonna have to wash you first.
Come on.
I'm...I'm sorry, I can't.
Of course you can.
You're shy.
I'm not.
Have another drink.
Gladly, but this, I can't do.
Believe me, no one is
more shocked than I am.
I hope it passes.
What will I do in my spare time?
Go for a piss, let it stopped
No need to worry, I was just...
Oh...
I thought you were someone else.
Show is almost over.
I'm sure the girls inside
will be happy to oblige.
You made some kind of mistake. Why don't you
tell me what you think you are doing and...
I'm taking you to the Queen.
Transcript by honeybunny & No1
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net